<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaylalife</title>
    <link>https://kayla.life/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kaylalife</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 19:58:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kayla.life/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Surrender to Life</title>
      <link>https://kayla.life/blog/2020-04-08-surrender-to-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 19:58:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kayla.life/blog/2020-04-08-surrender-to-life/</guid>
      <description>I feel a burning sensation in the center of my chest, at the same time as calmness is softly raining down on me. Making an effort to breath deeply brings ease.
Clarity, confusion, chaos, pain.
Knowingness, vibration, trust, love.
I commit to live this life fully.
I commit to express my truth.
I surrender to life force.
I bow to the divine.
My deepest committment is to follow the vibration of life force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I envision my work life in tech</title>
      <link>https://kayla.life/blog/2019-11-28-tech-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 12:59:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kayla.life/blog/2019-11-28-tech-vision/</guid>
      <description>There are many different shades to being part of the tech world. I feel grateful for having experienced many moments of feeling home and part of this world thanks to some of the smaller communities. It is a wonderful feeling to meet likeminded people and together geek out about the things we are passionate about.
On the other side of the coin are the tensions and struggles I notice for myself and the larger collective of people working in tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community with lots of heart</title>
      <link>https://kayla.life/blog/2019-08-16-community-with-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:38:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kayla.life/blog/2019-08-16-community-with-heart/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been two weeks now since Heart of Clojure. Time for reflections. 🌟
I feel much movement within, a sense of wonder, a pinch of surprise and a big portion of gratitude. It was a special conference for me.
The Background Story A while ago, I made a promise to myself. I decided to accept every possibility to speak in front of people. In the past, having all attention on me was one of the most frightening moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Determination</title>
      <link>https://kayla.life/blog/2019-02-25-determination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 22:35:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kayla.life/blog/2019-02-25-determination/</guid>
      <description>I have learned to listen closely to my mind. How am I talking to myself? What thoughts are crossing my mind at any moment? What are the underlying believes that shape how I live my life?
I know that things can change faster than we believe is possible. Focus and determination can go a long way. I shift the way I think, so does my reality. I hear the voice of a dear friend of mine:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Movement is my Medicine</title>
      <link>https://kayla.life/blog/2018-09-24-movement-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 21:39:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kayla.life/blog/2018-09-24-movement-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Another Friday evening. I jump on my bike and feel a smile on my face. Hello, Berlin. You are gray, cold and wet today, but I feel warm inside and excited about the days ahead of me.
About half a year ago, I kept hearing about something that is called Movement Medicine. I had no idea what is was, but my intuition took me right into a space of freedom, connection and acceptance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going from Blockage to Flow</title>
      <link>https://kayla.life/blog/2018-08-19-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 22:52:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kayla.life/blog/2018-08-19-flow/</guid>
      <description>My motivation for writing this post The topics I&amp;rsquo;ve always been most enthusiastic about are human connections and everything connected to how we navigate through life. Recently, the conversations I&amp;rsquo;ve been having brought similar questions to the surface. Many are wondering:
 Why am I feeling tired and sluggish most of the days? How can I feel less stressed and more at ease? How can I resolve conflicts with people I am working with?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Commit Flow with Tig</title>
      <link>https://kayla.life/blog/2018-01-25-how-to-use-tig/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 18:30:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kayla.life/blog/2018-01-25-how-to-use-tig/</guid>
      <description>Minimal tig keybindings to make the most out of your commit flow. It was at my first programming internship that one of my collegues showed me how to use tig. It is a text-mode interface that offers a more interactive and flexibel way of developing compared to using git with the command line only. I have been using it ever since and I feel more productive and in control of my commit flow.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>